[{"answer": "Well, obviously, I'm a little am disappointed.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Mr. Rominger, what is your reaction to the conviction?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "Well, you know, you have to understand, Joe has worked tirelessly.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "What was all that about?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "We will appeal.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Is your intention not to appeal?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Jerry did want to testify but we never made a commitment in the sense we were 100 percent positive.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Why was that?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "My personal feeling about Jerry Sandusky is that this is the first time that he has ever been held accountable for what he has done.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "What is your feeling about Sandusky?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "No, at this point, the facts are still developing.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Will they be pursuing civil action, either of your clients?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what should happen next.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "What is your sense of what should happen next?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Let me go to Sara Ganim, who is the Harrisburg \"Patriot News\" reporter who broke the story.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Are they so blinded by the aura of bib sports in this country that they did not do anything?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Well, it's not about what I think, Piers.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Well, I know that Jerry Sandusky's attorney got up on the podium behind and said that he is still innocent, that he intends to fight this on appeal.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Well, I tend to think in terms of how victims and people who have been through this experience, how they're going to respond to it because I deal with that so much.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "What's your reaction to the culmination of this trial?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "He is, you know, in the extent that -- it depends on how you interpret what he is saying.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Is Sandusky a classic pedophile predator?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "You feel vindicated.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "What is your feeling seeing somebody like Sandusky be convicted, be brought to book?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "It is the most unbelievable amount of courage you could ever imagine, you see what I go through right now.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Having been through it, what kind of courage did it take for these victims to get on the stand, do you think?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Evil, just pure, pure evil.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "And, Michael, what are your feelings toward a man like Sandusky?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Is he a classic sexual predator?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Truly is an experience that you can't necessarily get over, even reliving and the courage that they had to testify is retraumatization.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "But what do you say to them to get over the experience they have had at the hands of this monster?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Well, I think this is an enormous opportunity for everyone has anything to do with children, whether its schools, whether its camps, any program that deals with children, to start educating the staff, the children, the parents.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What do we do about that, do you think, looking forward, what do we do?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Well, it is hard to say that she lied.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Dr. Janet, very quickly, about a Dottie Sandusky, who did take the stand, unlike Jerry Sandusky, and defended her husband, sort of practicing the \"see no, hear no, speak no evil\" philosophy of defense, I did not see anything, I didn't hear anything, do you think that she lied or is she just in some denial about all of this?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "I'm only trying to achieve one thing.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "But what are you trying to achieve with the cable news genre, if anything?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "It was interesting to do the speech, to work on the speech.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "When you said it, did you believe it yourself?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, let me just back up a little bit and say, I don't have to live in the real world.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "If you were running a news network, what would you do?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Well, I have no idea.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "I mean, just talking up from your character's speech at the start of the first episode, are Americans still the hardest-working people on earth?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "You didn't write that speech?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "No, no, of course you're not.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Am I being too cynical here?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Well, I liked it then because of the drug use.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "But why do you like that solitude?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "You know what, I don't -- the last thing I want to do is make drugs sound good to anybody.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "And did you, like the Beatles, do your best stuff on the drugs?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Yes, I..", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Have you arrived at a good place in your life now do you think?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I'm the luckiest guy in the world.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "The hard way maybe, but you have?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Every so often -- I am a single man.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "And without wishing to be too intrusive here, according to the photographs I saw after the premiere, you are dating a beautiful woman from \"Sex in the City,\" is this true?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "10:00 p.m.", "docId": "120622pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "That's \"The Newsroom,\" Sunday, on HBO, time?", "qSentId": 555}]